Diego Raul Rojas Camargo

Peru • Arequipa • devup2332@gmail.com • +51976469908 • https://drojascam.com

Summary

I'm a full stack developer from Peru with over 3 years of experience in frontend and backend development applications.

I always tend to implement the best solution that I find for each task assigned to me having good communication with my work team

Education

San Agustin University
Bachelor Telecommunications Engineering
2019

Peru, Arequipa

Experience

Lapzo Full Stack Engineer Mexico City May 2022 – August 2024

- Maintenance of the main application of the company developed with React, Vitejs, Hasura, Graphql and RadixUI
- During this work I was solving bugs and creating new functionalities for the application both in the backend and in the frontend.
- Creation of differents scripts to solve specific problems in the platform using Nodejs as environment

Inetum Frontend Engineer Peru, Lima

September 2021 – May 2022

- Front End development for an application developed with Nextjs, React, Express, Material UI, ApolloServer and GraphQL.
- A redesign of the application was carried out to manage the company's back office
- A microservices system was developed to manage sales and new product orders.

Jabu Frontend Engineer Peru, Lima

March 2021 - August 2021

- I was working on a new version of this company's main application with NextJs , Prisma and Typescript
- Something that was taken into account was the optimization of each aspect of the application

Skills

Technical: Javascript | Typescript | Nodejs | React | Nextjs | Nestjs | Redux

Language: Spanish and English